RI from today's internet headlines it's
rapid
refresh Batman Arkham Knight is the
latest installment of the Blockbuster
video game franchise it came out Tuesday
in case you were wondering why the nerds
in your life aren't responding to
texts most notably it's the first game
of the series where you can drive the
Batmobile
yeah and you know you you know your
standard stable of villains you got your
Joker your penguin your Riddler but as
they keep making more and more of these
games the Batman Rogues Galler is
getting stretched pretty thin so
panelist what's a lame Batman villain we
might see in the future anyone Lauren
The Tickler yes points that would drive
me crazy that would drive me crazy I
cannot stand to be tickled like not even
fun he just pins you down no no God that
would be the yeah yeah Ryan Harley Quinn
Medicine Woman yes oh my God it was
right there the whole time right there
perfect moving on R&B music has a rich
and oily tradition of sexually
suggestive titles like let's get it on
and sexual healing and the 90s slow jam
throwback genuine has released a new
song that gives a hearty middle finger
to subtlety coming soon to a filthy
airport at Jason strip club near you
leave it
in leave it in why not just leave it in
the whole
time
here's a fun fact here's a fun fact
genuine has uh eight kids himself so
maybe his next song should be called
yank it out or finishing her hair for a
change um panelist what's an even less
subtle title for an R&B slow jam than
leave it in actually whose dick is this
it's
mine it's mine it's not done yet it's
not done yet she's got more he's got
more I got more it's whose dick is this
it's m mine and soon it'll be yours yes
all right good Bo I would feel like
that's I just needed to say the first
part that's if a dick you didn't
recognize texted you is who dick is
this